<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<RatePageMetaTag xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

  <MetaTags>

    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>1</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>130</CountryTo>
      <Title>Cheapest Calling Cards to India from USA | Best International Phone Cards to India from USA | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>="Raza: Search the best rates to call India and worldwide from USA. No hidden fees and amazing call quality. Choose your plan and start saving money today!</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Cheap Calling Cards to India, International Phone Cards to India, Calling Cards to India from USA, Phone Cards to India</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>2</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>130</CountryTo>
      <Title>Calling India from Canada | Cheap Calls to India from Canada | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>Raza: Make cheap calls to any city in India from Canada for 1.3¢ per minute. Dedicated plans for landlines and mobile phones to help you save money.</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Calling India From Canada, Cheap Calls to India From Canada</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>3</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>130</CountryTo>
      <Title>Cheap International Calls to India | Calling India from the UK | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>Raza: Calling India from UK? We offer the best plans for calls to India from the UK. Sign up for free and call India for less!</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Calls to India, Cheap International Calls to India, Calling India from UK</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>


    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>1</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>238</CountryTo>
      <Title>Call Pakistan from USA | Cheap Calls to Pakistan from USA | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>Raza: Make cheap calls to Pakistan from USA, including calls to landlines and mobiles at just 7.5¢/min. Check out our Pakistan phone calling plans.</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Call Pakistan from USA, Cheap Calls to Pakistan from USA</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>2</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>238</CountryTo>
      <Title>Cheap Calls to Pakistan | Best Call Rates to Pakistan From Canada | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>Raza: Looking to call Pakistan from Canada? Make cheap calls to Pakistan, including calls to landlines and mobiles with our popular and reliable plans.</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Cheap Calls to Pakistan, Best Call Rates to Pakistan</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>3</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>238</CountryTo>
      <Title>Cheap Calls to Pakistan From UK | Calling Plans for Mobiles and Landlines | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>Raza: Promising you the lowest call rates to Pakistan from UK, with great call quality and amazing customer service.</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Cheap Calls to Pakistan</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

    <MetaTagInfo>
        <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
        <CountryFrom>1</CountryFrom>
        <CountryTo>27</CountryTo>
        <Title>Call Bangladesh From USA | Cheap Calls to Bangladesh | Raza</Title>
        <PageDescription>Raza: Make cheap calls to anywhere in Bangladesh like Dhaka, Chittagong and more at just 3¢/min, with exceptional call quality and amazing customer service.</PageDescription>
        <PageKeywords>Call Bangladesh From USA</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>2</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>27</CountryTo>
      <Title>Call Bangladesh from Canada | Cheap Calls to Bangladesh | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>Raza: Make low cost calls to Bangladesh from your landline or mobile at 3¢/min. Our calling plans to Bangladesh from Canada deliver fantastic call quality.</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Call Bangladesh from Canada</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

    <MetaTagInfo>
      <PageName>RatePage</PageName>
      <CountryFrom>3</CountryFrom>
      <CountryTo>27</CountryTo>
      <Title>Call Bangladesh from UK | Cheap Calls to Bangladesh | Raza</Title>
      <PageDescription>Raza: An industry pioneer, creating reliable and affordable calling plans to Bangladesh from the UK. Crystal clear call quality at the most competitive prices is an assurance.</PageDescription>
      <PageKeywords>Call Bangladesh from UK</PageKeywords>
    </MetaTagInfo>

  </MetaTags>    

</RatePageMetaTag>